http://www.trivenigroup.com/sugarmicrosite/privacy-policy-suger.html

Sugar ProductionSugar ProductionA manufacturing and engineering solutions conglomerate with operations in sugar production, power co-generation, distillery, industrial gearing and water treatment solutions, Triveni services key priority sectors of sugar, power generation and water management with its 10 manufacturing locations across India. Triveni is listed on country’s leading stock exchanges – BSE and NSE.Business OverviewFacilitiesCane DevelopmentProcessOur ClientsQuality StandardCertificationContact usCo-GenerationCo-GenerationBusiness OverviewFacilitiesTechnologyContact UsDistilleryDistilleryBusiness OverviewCustomer SegmentationContact usShagunHand SanitizersQuality PolicyEHSGroup SitesGroup SitesTriveni CorporateShagunGear & GearboxesWater & Wastewater Treatment Solutions
We are one of the leading
producers of SUGAR in India.
HomePrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you use our website. The policy may change from time to time, without any prior notice, so please check it regularly.
While using the site you may disclose your name, email address and some other information. Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you, the user, with better responses and high interactivity.
When you are on this website and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with Triveni alone, unless it is specifically stated otherwise. If the data is being collected and/or maintained by any company other than Triveni, you will be notified prior to the time of the data collection or transfer.
Please be aware that this website contains links to external websites and once you are on any external website, they may collect personally identifiable information about you. This privacy statement does not cover the information practices of those web sites linked from this website.
As a general rule, Triveni will not disclose or share any of your personally identifiable information except when Triveni has your permission or under special circumstances, such as when Triveni believes in good faith that the law requires it or as permitted in terms of this policy.
Triveni may also disclose account information in special cases when it has reasons to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Terms of Service or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) Triveni’s rights or property, other website users, or if Triveni deems it necessary to maintain, service, and improve its products and services.
As with all information, Triveni will never rent or sell your personal, financial or other information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while Triveni strives to protect your personal information, Triveni cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Triveni and you do so at your own risk. Once Triveni receives your transmission, it makes best efforts to ensure its security on its systems.
HomeSite MapDisclaimer Privacy PolicyTerms & Conditions
© 2015 Triveni
Engineering & Industries Ltd.
